Let's begin our exploration of the AI
fluency
[Music]
framework. I'm Joe Feller. My name is
Drew. I'm Maggie Vo. My name is Rick
[Music]
Dacon. The focus of this course is not
really about AI as a technology.
Instead, it's mostly about you and I, us
humans, and how we interact and
collaborate with AI systems. We explore
AI fluency, our ability to engage with
AI systems in ways that are effective,
efficient, ethical, and safe. It's about
imagining possibilities that don't treat
AI as some sort of next level spellch
checker, but instead as a trusted
partner for doing creative and
innovative problem solving work. This
will help you develop an intuitive feel
for what generative AI can do and how
best to work with it. We're all learning
together how to navigate this rapidly
evolving landscape. This course is about
fundamentally shifting how we approach
AI.